<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Core Interaction Spring 2022</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Core Interaction Spring 2022</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://ci22.href.blue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Github</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/resources/01_github/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/resources/01_github/</guid><description>As a reminder, Git is a tool for version controlling your code. Your code is committed into repositories, where each project has its own repository. For this course, all projects and assignments will be organized into one repository. GitHub is a service that hosts a copy of your git repository online. This makes it easy for others to contribute to, and most importantly host it online as a website.
At this point your repository on your computer probably looks like this:</description></item><item><title>JavaScript</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/resources/02_javascript/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/resources/02_javascript/</guid><description>Some tutorials on JavaScript:
W3 Schools Async lectures from previous semesters. Password is interaction: 1, 2 Some examples from class:
Hello, World &amp;lt;!DOCTYPE html&amp;gt; &amp;lt;html&amp;gt; &amp;lt;head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;body&amp;gt; &amp;lt;script&amp;gt; // We&amp;#39;re calling a built in function called alert, // and passing in a string with &amp;#34;Hello, World!&amp;#34; alert(&amp;#39;Hello, World!&amp;#39;); &amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/body&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/html&amp;gt; Call and Response // Declare a variable that will change called response // and set its value to an empty string (containing nothing) let response = &amp;#39;&amp;#39;; // Declare a variable called name (that is a constant // and will not change).</description></item><item><title>People</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/people/</guid><description>STUDENTS
Anna Blyumenkrants (gh) Hugo Chao (gh) Gayoung Do (gh) Themis Kung (gh) Haylee Lee (gh) Talita Ozkok (gh) Ines Andrea Penaud (gh) Kiara Putrilia (gh) Anthony Rangel Apreza (gh) Jiyeong Shin (gh) Hannah Suh (gh) Sophie Tsang (gh) Gianna Waldron (gh) Shiyao Wu (gh) Wu Tong (gh) Hallie Young (gh) INSTRUCTORS
Sophie Auger Eric Li</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/projects/</guid><description>All work is expected to be hosted on Github Pages. You are expected to create and maintain an index.html of all work produced during this course and keep it up to date.
Projects P1: Cross-Platform Storytelling P2: Stories as Networks P3: Elastic Collections P4: Input/Output Studio Exercises Slack Avatar Screen Time Handmade Code Interaction &amp;amp; Type Study Hover States Flexbox Things that go beep Favicon Filter Lab Assignments A1: Semantics are everything</description></item><item><title>Readings</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/readings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/readings/</guid><description>Thoughts and responses relating to studio readings are expected be collected here
Unit 1 discussion questions / comments Unit 2 discussion questions / comments Unit 3 discussion questions / comments Unit 4
Reading leaders signup sheet Unit 1: Interaction with the Internet Studio Readings
Olia Lialina, Vernacular Web, 2007 Jill Lepore, Can the Internet be Archived?, 2015 Amanda Hess, Slack Off: How workplace chat is changing office culture, 2018 Lab Readings</description></item><item><title>Syllabus</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/syllabus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/syllabus/</guid><description>Core Interaction comprises two courses, taken concurrently: studio and lab. Together, they form the foundation for interaction design and practice on the web.
Studio meets twice a week and will provide a thorough and elaborate study of interactive concepts and techniques for applications. We will conduct an extensive investigation into the interface, mechanism, controls, and aims of interactive works. Students will learn how to design and develop complex interactive projects, undertaking comprehensive research and directing their thinking process from brainstorming to final outcome.</description></item><item><title>Week 1</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week1/</guid><description>WEEK 1 (REMOTE) Tue 1/25 Studio IN CLASS Introductions (Sophie and Eric) Fill out the Questionnaire Group Agreement Review Syllabus Intro: Reading assignments sign up Begin Unit 1: Intx with the Internet Exercise: Slack Avatar AFTER CLASS READ + WATCH
Cyberspace Origins (lecture) &amp;amp; Internet Today (lecture) on vimeo, check Slack for the password Olia Lialina (reading) Everyone writes a discussion comment or question here. Reading leaders, please connect the readings to the two lectures and prepare comments and questions around this.</description></item><item><title>Week 10</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week10/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week10/</guid><description>WEEK 10 Tue 4/5 Studio In Class Reading discussion, Haylee is our discussion leader After Class Thu 4/7 Studio In Class After Class Fri 4/8 Lab In Class After Class</description></item><item><title>Week 11</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week11/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week11/</guid><description>WEEK 11 Tue 4/12 Studio In Class After Class Thu 4/14 Studio In Class After Class Fri 4/15 Lab In Class After Class</description></item><item><title>Week 12</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week12/</guid><description>WEEK 12 Tue 4/19 Studio In Class After Class Thu 4/21 Studio In Class After Class Fri 4/22 Lab In Class After Class</description></item><item><title>Week 13</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week13/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week13/</guid><description>WEEK 13 Tue 4/26 Studio In Class After Class Thu 4/28 Studio In Class After Class Fri 4/29 Lab In Class After Class</description></item><item><title>Week 14</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week14/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week14/</guid><description>WEEK 14 Tue 5/3 Studio In Class After Class Thu 5/5 Studio In Class After Class Fri 5/6 Lab In Class After Class</description></item><item><title>Week 15</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week15/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week15/</guid><description>WEEK 15 Tue 5/10 Studio In Class After Class Thu 5/12 Studio In Class After Class Fri 5/13 Lab In Class After Class</description></item><item><title>Week 2</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week2/</guid><description>WEEK 2 (REMOTE) Tue 2/1 Studio In Class Discuss lectures + readings. Hannah is our discussion leader. Today&amp;rsquo;s Notes Small group meetings to discuss project ideas in groups of 3-4 ambient work time (Exercise: Screen Time) After Class P1: Part 2 Finish Exercise: Screen Time Thu 2/3 Studio In Class Small group crits: Implementation Today&amp;rsquo;s Notes Organizing Files for the Web File Structure Demo After Class P1: Part 4 Read Amanda Hess, Slack Off: How workplace chat is changing office culture &amp;amp; add write your comments/questions in the Unit 1 Reading document.</description></item><item><title>Week 3</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week3/</guid><description>WEEK 3 Tue 2/8 Studio In Class Discuss lectures + readings (Sophie is our discussion leader) P1: Final crit with Sophie &amp;amp; Eric Review What&amp;rsquo;s the point of critique Last person who presented is first to speak about next presenter’s work After Class READ
Loretta Staples American Artist Frank Chimero WATCH
Digital Typography and Language in User Interfaces Bias within Design Systems Write your comments/questions in the Unit 2 Reading document</description></item><item><title>Week 4</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week4/</guid><description>WEEK 4 Tue 2/15 Studio In Class Today&amp;rsquo;s notes Small group critique: review ideas Exercise: HANDMADE CODE Ambient work time: P2: Part 2 After Class Complete P2: Part 2 Make sure your Github is linked to the class website and that all your links are working. Thu 2/17 Studio In Class Lectures: Responsive Web + Typography on the Web (access with newschool email) Today&amp;rsquo;s notes Review P2: Part 2 + references After Class P2: Part 3 Fri 2/18 Lab In Class Lecture</description></item><item><title>Week 5</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week5/</guid><description>WEEK 5 Tue 2/22 Studio In Class Today&amp;rsquo;s Notes Exercise: Typographic Explorations Small Group reviews + ambient work time After Class P2: Part 4 Thu 2/24 Studio In Class Today&amp;rsquo;s Notes Exercise: Hover States Ambient Work time + optional 1:1s After Class P2: Part 5 Complete Exercise: Hover States and add to your Github Fri 2/25 Lab In Class LECTURE</description></item><item><title>Week 6</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week6/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week6/</guid><description>WEEK 6 Tue 3/1 Studio In Class Today&amp;rsquo;s Notes Part 5 pair reviews + 1:2s check-ins After Class P2, Part 6 Check out this event (today, 6:30pm) And this podcast (maybe listen while coding&amp;hellip;) Thu 3/3 Studio In Class Today&amp;rsquo;s Notes Part 6 reviews + Small Group check-ins After Class Project 2, Part 7 (complete project) Fri 3/4 Lab In Class TECHNICAL</description></item><item><title>Week 7</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week7/</guid><description>WEEK 7 Tue 3/8 Studio In Class Today&amp;rsquo;s Notes Critique: Stories as Networks After Class Review Stories as Networks projects and identify a couple that stood out to you. Watch Dynamic Use of Data Read Sharing as Survival: Mindy Seu on the Cyberfeminism Index and write one discussion comment/question. Themis will be our discussion leader. Thu 3/10 Studio In Class Mid-semester survey Reading discussion: Hear from Themis about Sharing as Survival and Dynamic Use of Data.</description></item><item><title>Week 8</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week8/</guid><description>WEEK 8 Tue 3/22 Studio In Class Hear from Gianna and discuss Data Feminism Review Exercise: Flexbox Calendar Discuss project ideas in small groups Exercise: Things that go beep Project 3: Part 2 After Class Watch Documenting your Work (video lecure) Read The Hidden Life of an Amazon User (Haylee is our discussion leader) and write one discussion question/comment Project 3: Part 2 Thu 3/24 Studio In Class Cancelled After Class Project 3: Part 3 Fri 3/25 Lab In Class Review Assignment</description></item><item><title>Week 9</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/schedule/week9/</guid><description>WEEK 9 Tue 3/29 Studio In Class Review collections Today&amp;rsquo;s notes Exercise: Filter P3, Part 4 + 5 After Class P3, Part 5 Thu 3/31 Studio In Class Reading Discussion (Haylee is our discussion leader) Review Exercise: Things That Go Beep Review P3, Part 5 Today&amp;rsquo;s notes Exercise: Filter After Class P3, Part 6 Finish Exercise: Filter Fri 4/1 Lab In Class After Class</description></item></channel></rss>