<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Core Interaction Spring 2022</title><link>http://ci22.eric.young.li/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Core Interaction Spring 2022</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://ci22.eric.young.li/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>People</title><link>http://ci22.eric.young.li/people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.eric.young.li/people/</guid><description>Students Anna Blyumenkrants Gayoung Do Rose Henderschedt Themis Kung Haylee Lee Talita Ozkok Ines Andrea Penaud Kiara Putrilia Anthony Rangel Apreza Jiyeong Shin Hannah Suh Sophie Tsang Gianna Waldron Shiyao Wu Instructors Sophie Auger Eric Li</description></item><item><title>Readings</title><link>http://ci22.eric.young.li/readings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.eric.young.li/readings/</guid><description> Reading leaders signup sheet FURTHER READING
Anny Li, How to Encounter a Puddle, 2018 Ursula K. LeGuin, Carrier Bag Theory of Fiction, 1986 Internetting with Amanda Hess, ongoing Shannon Mattern, Things that Go Beep, 2018 Alexandra Lange, The Woman Who Gave the Macintosh a Smile, 2018 Beatriz Colomina and Mark Wigley, Are We Human?: Notes on an Archaeology of Design (Introduction), 2016 Aria Dean &amp;amp; Martine Syms, Growing Up Google, 2017 Marjanne van Helvert, Dirty Design Margarat Anderson, In Web Design, Accessibility Shouldn’t Be an Afterthought, 2020 Silas Munro, Typography as a Radical Act, 2019 Ruben Pater, The Politics of Design, 2016 Anne Friedberg, Virtual Window, 2006 (Excerpt) Mimi Onuoha and Mother Cyborg, People’s Guide to AI, 2018 VPRO, The Real Value of Your Personal Data, 2013 video David Reinfurt, &amp;ldquo;Muriel Cooper&amp;rdquo;, 2018 video Natalie Cecire, Apple’s Modernism, Google’s Modernism, 2015 Maciej Ceglowski, Web Design: The First 100 Years, 2014 Louise Drulhe, Critical Atlas of Internet Jenny Odell, How to do Nothing, 2017 Paul Ford, Reboot the World, 2016 Siva Vaidhyanathan, Open Source as Culture/Culture as Open Source, 2005 Danah Boyd, Participating in the Always-On Lifestyle, 2015 Rem Koolhaas, Junkspace, 2002 Allessandro Ludovico, Post-Digital Print, 2012</description></item><item><title>Resources</title><link>http://ci22.eric.young.li/resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.eric.young.li/resources/</guid><description>The technologies, languages, and libraries introduced in class are well documented online. If you are having difficulties, take time to troubleshoot online before asking for help. Good coding is good online searching!
Core 2 Class Lectures
Vimeo pw: interaction
Office hours with CD Tutors
Required Communication Design visiting lecture series:
Archived here
Fridays, 3–4pm
GETTING SETUP
Setting up Your Workspace What’s the Point of Critique? Basic file structure demo Github site template Organizing and Naming Files OTHER CLASS LINKS</description></item></channel></rss>