<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Core Interaction Spring 2022</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Core Interaction Spring 2022</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://ci22.href.blue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>People</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/people/</guid><description>STUDENTS
Anna Blyumenkrants Gayoung Do Rose Henderschedt Themis Kung Haylee Lee Talita Ozkok Ines Andrea Penaud Kiara Putrilia Anthony Rangel Apreza Jiyeong Shin Hannah Suh Sophie Tsang Gianna Waldron Shiyao Wu INSTRUCTORS
Sophie Auger Eric Li</description></item><item><title>Readings</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/readings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/readings/</guid><description>Reading leaders signup sheet UNIT 1 Studio Readings
Olia Lialina, Vernacular Web, 2007 Lab Readings
Paul Ford, What Is Code?, 2015 FURTHER READING
Anny Li, How to Encounter a Puddle, 2018 Ursula K. LeGuin, Carrier Bag Theory of Fiction, 1986 Internetting with Amanda Hess, ongoing Shannon Mattern, Things that Go Beep, 2018 Alexandra Lange, The Woman Who Gave the Macintosh a Smile, 2018 Beatriz Colomina and Mark Wigley, Are We Human?</description></item><item><title>Resources</title><link>http://ci22.href.blue/resources/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://ci22.href.blue/resources/</guid><description>The technologies, languages, and libraries introduced in class are well documented online. If you are having difficulties, take time to troubleshoot online before asking for help. Good coding is good online searching!
Core 2 Class Lectures
Vimeo pw: interaction
Office hours with CD Tutors
Required Communication Design visiting lecture series:
Archived here
Fridays, 3–4pm
GETTING SETUP
Setting up Your Workspace What’s the Point of Critique? Basic file structure demo Github site template Organizing and Naming Files OTHER CLASS LINKS</description></item></channel></rss>